<resources>
    <string name="app_name">News Nest</string>
    <string name="tab_title_top_news">Top news</string>
    <string name="tab_title_world_news">World news</string>
    <string name="tab_title_bookmarks">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="tab_title_more_news">More news</string>
    <string name="tab_title_article">Article</string>
    <string name="date_of_publish">Date of publish:</string>
    <string name="no_bookmarks">No bookmarks found. Start saving your favorites!</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_title">Error</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">An unknown error occurred.</string>
    <string name="terms_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="terms_decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_title">Terms and Conditions</string>

    <string name="app_title">News Nest</string>
    <string name="org_name">Beaver Inc.</string>
    <string name="contact_email">newsnest@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
        <![CDATA[
            Welcome to %1$s!\n

            These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of %2$s\'s mobile application, %1$s, located at [Your App\'s Website or Contact Information].

            By accessing this app, we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use %1$s if you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.\n

            \n<b>License</b>\n

            Unless otherwise stated, %2$s and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on %1$s. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from %1$s for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.

            \nYou must not:\n

            - Republish material from %1$s\n
            - Sell, rent, or sub-license material from %1$s\n
            - Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from %1$s\n
            - Redistribute content from %1$s\n

            This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof.\n

            \n<b>Privacy</b>\n

            Your use of %1$s is also governed by our Privacy Policy. Please review our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into these terms and conditions by reference.

            \n<b>Termination</b>\n

            We may terminate or suspend your account and bar access to %1$s immediately, without prior notice or liability, under our sole discretion, for any reason whatsoever and without limitation, including but not limited to a breach of the Terms.

            \n<b>Changes to This Agreement</b>\n

            We reserve the right to modify these Terms and Conditions at any time. We do so by posting and drawing attention to the updated terms on %1$s. Your decision to continue to visit and make use of %1$s after such changes have been made constitutes your formal acceptance of the new Terms and Conditions.

            \n<b>Contact Us</b>\n

            If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at %3$s.\n

            By using %1$s, you hereby consent to our Terms and Conditions and agree to its Privacy Policy.\n
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>